If you're thinking about selling golf balls you find out on the golf course, it's very easy to do.
My name is Jared Garbett, and I'm with Echo Farms Golf and Country Club, and I'm going to teach you how to sell golf balls you find on the golf course.
Collect the golf balls until you have several hundred golf balls, maybe even a thousand golf balls, and go to your local pro shop or local golf center and see if they have a refurbished golf ball center or see if they sell golf balls two for a dollar, three for a dollar.
Have a bargain golf ball bin.
Most places will buy the golf balls from you, and then resell them in their store.
Sometimes, you may wish to make it a hobby or a small job to go into the local ponds at golf courses, or into the woods, and search for golf balls there.
Be sure to check with your local golf course before doing so, but it should not be a problem.
Make sure that you always carry the golf balls back to the pro shop, and sell them back to the pro shop that you get the balls from.
After doing this, you should get a cut of the money, and maybe it'll make it worth your while.
That's how you sell golf balls you find out on the golf course.